<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications on my Home page</title>
    <link>https://ouardifaissal.github.io/homepage/./publication/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publications on my Home page</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Faissal Ouardi</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ouardifaissal.github.io/homepage/./publication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Extended to multi-tilde-bar regular expressions and efficient finite automata constructions</title>
      <link>https://ouardifaissal.github.io/homepage/./publication/emtb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouardifaissal.github.io/homepage/./publication/emtb/</guid>
      <description>Several algorithms have been designed to convert a regular expression into an equivalent finite automaton. One of the most popular constructions, due to Glushkov and to McNaughton and Yamada, is based on the computation of the Null, First, Last and Follow sets (called Glushkov functions) associated with a linearized version of the expression. Recently Mignot considered a family of extended expressions called Extended to multi-tilde-bar Regular Expressions (EmtbREs) and he showed that, under some restrictions, Glushkov functions can be defined for an EmtbRE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An efficient computation of the equation K-automaton of a regular K-expression</title>
      <link>https://ouardifaissal.github.io/homepage/./publication/kequation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ouardifaissal.github.io/homepage/./publication/kequation/</guid>
      <description>The aim of this paper is to describe a quadratic algorithm for computing the equation K-automaton of a regular K-expression as defined by Lombardy and Sakarovitch. Our construction is based on an extension to regular K-expressions of the notion of c-continuation that we introduced to compute the equation automaton of a regular expression as a quotient of its position automaton.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>